<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on NTU-NLP</title>
    <link>https://ntunlpsg.github.io/demo/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on NTU-NLP</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ntunlpsg.github.io/demo/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://ntunlpsg.github.io/demo/post/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntunlpsg.github.io/demo/post/news/</guid>
      <description>2018    &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;      15 Mar, 2018 NLP in the Era of Big Data, Deep Learning, and Post Truth workshop at ESSLLI 2018.   01 Mar, 2018 Our lab is looking for highly motivated PhD students and postdoc researchers to work in natural language processing, deep learning, and machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading group</title>
      <link>https://ntunlpsg.github.io/demo/post/reding-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntunlpsg.github.io/demo/post/reding-group/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Natural Language Processing (NLP) reading group meets regularly (usually weekly) to discuss research topics on a particular sub-field of NLP.
Subscription You can receive announcements about the reading group by joining our mailing list. To join the mailing list, please use an academic email address and send an email to ntunlpsg@gmail.com with a subject &amp;ldquo;subscribe ntu-nlp&amp;rdquo;. If you use a non-academic email address, we would have to verify it which could delay your subscription process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic: the website designer for Hugo</title>
      <link>https://ntunlpsg.github.io/demo/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntunlpsg.github.io/demo/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Academic is a framework to help you create a beautiful website quickly. Perfect for personal sites, blogs, or business/project sites. Check out the latest demo of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes. Then head on over to the Quick Start guide or take a look at the Release Notes.

Key features:
 Easily manage various content including homepage, blog posts, publications, talks, and projects Extensible via color themes and widgets/plugins Write in Markdown for easy formatting and code highlighting, with LaTeX for mathematical expressions Social/academic network linking, Google Analytics, and Disqus comments Responsive and mobile friendly Simple and refreshing one page design Multilingual and easy to customize  Color Themes Academic is available in different color themes and font themes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>